Guide to the Vassar College Dean of the College, Dean of the Faculty Records, 1917-1997 (bulk 1940-1996
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- CCP Minutes, 1980-1985; (5 folders) (Box 25)
- CCP's Work as a Committee, 3 Oct 1984 (Box 25)
- Masters of CCP Material (Box 25)
- Membership of CCP, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
- Subcommittee Meetings, 1981-1984 (Box 25)
- Faculty Notices, 1976-1984; (6 folders) (Box 25)
- Files [sent] to Storage [in] 1988: Faculty Legislation, 1941; (2 folders) (Box 25)
- Joint Committee Report, 1964 (Box 25)
- Count of Courses, 1954-1965; (5 folders) (Box 25)
- Committee on Prive. in Election, 1954-1962 (Box 25)
- Trustee Development Committee, 1968 (Box 25)
- Forward Planning Committee, May 1968 (Box 25)
- Chart of Accounts, 1 July 1966 (Box 25)
- Comprehensive Planning Committee, Sep 1968 (Box 25)
- Files [sent] to Storage [in] 1989: Academic Program, 1974 (Box 25)
- CCP - Calendar, 1987; (2 folders) (Box 25)
- [Faculty Development] F (Box 25)
- CCP - Bridge Program, 1976 (Box 26)
- CCP - Course Numbering, 1972 (Box 26)
- Credit System, 1980 (Box 26)
- Critical Languages, 1984 (Box 26)
- Curricular Changes in Other Colleges, 1983 (Box 26)
- Curricular Revisions of '81, Subcommittee Reports to CCP, 1980 (Box 26)
- Curricular Revisions of '81 Papers and Reports, 1982 (Box 26)
- Curricular Revision of '81 Papers and Reports April-Dec. '80, 1980 (Box 26)
- Curriculum, 1980 (Box 26)
- Curriculum Inquiries, 1979 (Box 26)
- Curricular Proposals on Breadth, Etc., 1978 (Box 26)
- Distribution Requirements, 1974 (Box 26)
- Drop/Add, 1982 (Box 26)
- Duke-Vassar Summer School in Germany, 1974 (Box 26)
- CCP - Educational Priorities Questionnaire, 1970 (Box 26)
- Courses on Ethical Issues, 1981 (Box 26)
- Examinations, 1979 (Box 26)
- Field Work, 1982 (Box 26)
- Field of Concentration, 1981 (Box 26)
- Financial Aid, 1980 (Box 26)
- General Studies, 1973 (Box 26)
- Ad Hoc Committee on Future of Geography, 1979 (Box 26)
- Subcommittee to Evaluate Grading System, 1978 (Box 26)
- CCP - Graduate Center, 1970 (Box 26)
- CCP - Graduate Programs, 1983 (Box 26)
- CCP - Committee on Honors, 1975; (2 folders) (Box 26)
- CCP - Hours of Instruction, 1980 (Box 26)
- CCP - Independent Work, 1980 (Box 26)
- CCP - Keller Plan, 1974 (Box 26)
- CCP - Mathematics, 1983 (Box 26)
- CCP - Overview Committee, 1980 (Box 26)
- CCP - Pending, 1976 (Box 26)
- CCP - Physical Education, 1984 (Box 26)
- CCP - Policy Decisions, 1980 (Box 26)
- Major in the Liberal Arts Proposal Paper, 1984 (Box 26)
- CCP - Provisional Grades, 1977 (Box 26)
- CCP - Senior Requirements, 1978 (Box 26)
- Student Enrollment Patterns, [personnel], 1977 (Box 26)
- CCP - Subcommittee on Enrollments, 1977 (Box 26)
- CCP - Subcommittee on Grants, 1977 (Box 26)
- Summer Courses, 1982 (Box 26)
- Summer Courses (away from college), 1982 (Box 26)
- Summer Credit, 1972 (Box 26)
- Task Force Report, 1980 (Box 26)
- Ungraded Work, 1982 (Box 26)
- Multidisciplinary (Box 26)
- Curricular Reform Task Force and General Reports, (4 folders) (Box 27)
- Report – The Vassar Investment Research Committee Report, 1978 (Box 27)
- Report on a Program of Case Testing and Feasibility Determination, 1979 (Box 27)
- Middle States Report, 1979 (Box 27)
- CCP, Sep 1974 - Apr 1977, 1977-1978; (4 folders) (Box 27)
- Assessment Committee Minutes, 1956 (Box 27)
- Files [sent] to Storage [in] 1989: Anthropology, 1984-1985; (2 folders) (Box 27)
- Art, 1980-1986; (4 folders) (Box 27)
- Taylor-Van Ingen Renovation (Box 27)
- Biology, 1980-1987; (5 folders) (Box 27)
- Assessment Committee Questionnaires, 1956 (Box 27)
- Assessment Committee – Committee only Meetings etc., Report of Committee (Box 27)
- Assessment Committee – Faculty Questionnaires (Box 27)
- Financial Aid – Admissions (Box 27)
- Library (Box 27)
- Art Gallery (Box 27)
- Music (Box 27)
- Vassar and China – St. John’s College (Box 27)
- New York Times Articles – 5th Berkshire Conference (Box 27)
- Art Gallery, 1977-1985; (5 folders) (Box 27)
- Chemistry, 1981-1987; (2 folders) (Box 28)
- Proposed Chemistry Building, (2 folders) (Box 28)
- Classics, 1980 (Box 28)
- Blegen, 1980-1986 (Box 28)
- Blegen Expenses (Box 28)
- Blegen Requisitions (Box 28)
- Computer Science, 1980-1986; (3 folders) (Box 28)
- Drama, 1980-1986; (3 folders) (Box 28)
- Economics, 1982-1987; (5 folders) (Box 28)
- Education, 1980-1986; (2 folders) (Box 28)
- Vassar Cary Arboretum (Box 28)
- Blegen House and Blegen Lectures, 1985-1988 (Box 28)
- S. Rousseas’ Report on 1978 Amendment to Age Discrimination in Employment Act of 1967 (Box 28)
- Sokol, Lech, The Koscinsko Foundation, 1983-1984 (Box 28)
- M.A. Drama (Box 28)
- Drama Dept. Report (Box 28)
- Poughkeepsie Film Project, 1971-1987 (Box 28)
- Annual Report, Office of Educational Services and Student Relations, 1977-1978 (Box 28)
- Annual Report - Dean of College/Faculty, 1977-1978, 1983-1984; (5 folders) (Box 28)
- Annual Report - Dean of College/Faculty, 1973, 1975-1977, 1982-1983; (9 folders) (Box 29)
- Committee on Future of College Report to Trustees, 1952 (Box 29)
- Salary Study, 1963; (2 folders) (Box 29)
- Budgets, 1979-1981 (Box 29)
- Files [sent] to Storage [in] 1989: English, 1978-1986; (2 folders) (Box 29)
- French, 1980-1987 (Box 29)
- Geology and Geography, 1980-1987; (5 folders) (Box 29)
- Hispanic Study, 1980-1986; (3 folders) (Box 29)
- Latin American Studies (Box 29)
- Vassar/Wesleyan Program, (2 folders) (Box 29)
- History, 1980-1986; (2 folders) (Box 29)
- Italian, 1980-1987 (Box 29)
- German, 1980-1986 (Box 29)
- Math, 1980-1987 (Box 30)
- Music, 1980-1987; (2 folders) (Box 30)
- Philosophy, 1980-1983 (Box 30)
- Athletics (Box 30)
- Subcommittee on Athletics (Box 30)
- Athletics Budget Survey (Box 30)
- Physical Education/Dance, 1980-1987; (6 folders) (Box 30)
- Phys. Ed. Building (Box 30)
- Majors Reports - Coaches (Box 30)
- Report of the Comprehensive Planning Committee, 1968; (11 folders) (Box 30)
- Appendices to the Report of the Comprehensive Planning Committee, 1968; (1 folders) (Box 30)
- Files [sent] to Storage [in] 1989: Political Science, 1980-1986; (3 folders) (Box 31)
- Psychology, 1980-1986; (5 folders) (Box 31)
- Russian, 1980-1987; (2 folders) (Box 31)
- Sociology, 1982-1985; (2 folders) (Box 31)
- Africana Studies, 1980-1986; (7 folders) (Box 31)
- American Culture, 1980-1987; (6 folders) (Box 31)
- Asian Studies, 1980-1987; (3 folders) (Box 31)
- Cognitive Science, 1985-1987; (3 folders) (Box 31)
- Independent Studies, 1980-1984 (Box 31)
- International Studies, 1985-1987; (2 folders) (Box 31)
- Chicago Hall, 1980-1984 (Box 31)
- Annual Report Vassar Art Gallery, 1985-1986 (Box 31)
- Files [sent] to Storage [in] 1988: Faculty Budget, [personnel], 1976-1978; (2 folders) (Box 31)
- Faculty Salary Recommendations [personnel], 1981-1982; (2 folders) (Box 31)
- Physics, 1980-1987; (2 folders) (Box 31)
- Faculty Reviews, 1977-1978 (Box 31)
- Faculty Promotions/Re-appointments [personnel], 1978-1979; (3 folders) (Box 32)
- Dept. Recommendations [personnel], 1971, 1974; (2 folders) (Box 32)
- Mellon Committee, 1950-1952, 1962-1963; (3 folders) (Box 32)
- "A Competency based Program Proposal - Elementary Teacher Education,”, 1975; (2 folders) (Box 32)
- Vassar Farm Proposal, National Audubon Society, 1974 (Box 32)
- Academic Building Committee, 1955 (Box 32)
- Vassar-Yale Report, 1967 (Box 32)
- Resource Book, Financial Aid (Box 32)
- Committee on New Dimensions Report, 1967 (Box 32)
- "The Vassar Institute for the Advancement of College and University Teaching,", 1969 (Box 32)
- American Engineering Education for the Mid Hudson Region (Box 32)
- Committee on New Dimensions preliminary report, 1967 (Box 32)
- Appendices to Report of Comprehensive Planning Committee (Box 32)
- Committee on Academic Buildings 1959 (Box 32)
- Universities and World Affairs/ Carnegie Endowment for International Peace (Box 32)
- Faculty Student Ratio Report, 1958-1959 (Box 32)
- Report of Comprehensive Planning Committee, 1968 (Box 32)
- Brochure "The New Vassar" (Box 32)
- Private Higher Education, ACC, 1976 (Box 32)
- Academic Advisors Handbook (Box 32)
- Regents Tentative Statewide Plan for Development of Post-secondary Education, 1976 (Box 32)
- Mellon Committee Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 32)
- Brochure: Notes from Vassar (Box 32)
- A Competency-Based Program Proposal: Secondary Teacher Education, 1977; (2 folders) (Box 33)
- Files [sent] to storage [in] 1989: Language Fellows, 1983-1988; (5 folders) (Box 33)
- Language Assistants, 1984-1987; (3 folders) (Box 33)
- CCP Review of STS Program, 1975 (Box 33)
- Urban Studies, 1980-1985; (2 folders) (Box 33)
- Women's Studies, 1980-1987; (6 folders) (Box 33)
- Departments Reporting to Dean, 1985-1986 (Box 33)
- New Appointments, 1981-1982 (Box 33)
- Education Administration Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 33)
- Budget - Office and Personnel, 1948-1958 (Box 33)
- Budget - Office and Other, 1958 (Box 33)
- Institute of Foreign Languages (Box 33)
- Language Interns, [personnel], 1980-1982; (3 folders) (Box 33)
- Science, Technology, and Society, 1980-1986; (5 folders) (Box 33)
- Critical Social Thought, 1981-1982 (Box 33)
- Personnel Budget, 1958-1959 (Box 34)
- Department Recommendations, 1975 (Box 34)
- Faculty Salary Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 34)
- Advertising, 1980-1985; (4 folders) (Box 34)
- Vassar Fund Lectures, 1978-1986; (8 folders) (Box 34)
- Vassar Fund Budget Records, 1980-1982; (2 folders) (Box 34)
- Smith Fund, 1981-1985; (4 folders) (Box 34)
- Novy, 1981-1986; (5 folders) (Box 34)
- Novy Budget Records, 1980-1982; (2 folders) (Box 34)
- Honor Society Lecture Funds, 1981-1985; (5 folders) (Box 34)
- Vassar Art Gallery, Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 34)
- Annual Report, 1985-1986; (2 folders) (Box 34)
- Miscellaneous Annual Reports, 1985 (Box 34)
- Audio Visual Resource Center (AVRC), Annual Report, 1984-2985 (Box 34)
- Center for Career Development and Field Work, Annual Report, 1984-1985 (Box 34)
- Smith Budget Records, 1980-1982; (2 folders) (Box 34)
- Smith Correspondence (Box 34)
- Novy Smith Correspondence, 1979-1981; (2 folders) (Box 34)
- Advertising, 1985-1986; (3 folders) (Box 35)
- Office Career Planning, 1971-1976 (Box 35)
- Alum. Assistant, 1975-1977; (3 folders) (Box 35)
- D.O. Field Work, 1977-1979 (Box 35)
- Grants: NEH/NSF, 1969-1975; (3 folders) (Box 35)
- Workload (Box 35)
- Dean of Studies, 1971-1976; (2 folders) (Box 35)
- Elizabeth Daniels, (2 folders) (Box 35)
- Office of Career Services and Field Work, 1979 (Box 35)
- Field Work - Minutes (Box 35)
- Public Relations (Box 35)
- Faculty Salary Budget [personnel], 1978-1987; (8 folders) (Box 36)
- Operating Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 36)
- Salary Recommendations Library [personnel], 1984-1986; (2 folders) (Box 36)
- News Office, (2 folders) (Box 36)
- Department Chairman, 1982-1986 (Box 36)
- Mellon Committee Minutes, 1953-1957; (2 folders) (Box 36)
- Mellon Committee - Several Folders, 1952; (8 folders) (Box 36)
- Cresap, McCormick, Paget Report, 1951; (2 folders) (Box 36)
- H. Patrick Sullivan's Speeches, (4 folders) (Box 36)
- H.P. Sullivan's Advisee - Sarah Jessep (Box 36)
- General Statistics RE: Faculty (Box 37)
- Confidential Financial Planning, 1971 (Box 37)
- Copies for Mrs. Eurich (Box 37)
- Charles Griffin, Dean of Faculty Pending (Box 37)
- Dean's Office - September (Box 37)
- Examination Schedule, 1969 (Box 37)
- Dean Sullivan, Personal, 1978-1986; (6 folders) (Box 37)
- Dean Sullivan Recommendations [personnel] (Box 37)
- Garnsey Fund, 1981-1986 (Box 37)
- Dean of Faculty - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 38)
- Class and Section Count, 1961-1966 (Box 38)
- Urban Teacher Corps (Box 38)
- Teacher Training Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 38)
- Master of Arts in Teaching (MAT), (11 folders) (Box 38)
- NYS Teacher Certification, (6 folders) (Box 38)
- 5 College Project, (8 folders) (Box 38)
- TEDVC, (13 folders) (Box 38)
- MAT Proposals (Box 38)
- Study of MAT Program at Vassar, (2 folders) (Box 38)
- Curriculum Committee Minutes, 1948-1967; (19 folders) (Box 39)
- College Research Center Reports, 1965-1967; (2 folders) (Box 39)
- Curricular Committee Changes in Offerings, 1961-1968; (7 folders) (Box 39)
- Curriculum - Miscellaneous, 1960-1967; (7 folders) (Box 39)
- Budget Appropriation Sheets, July 1968 - June 1969 (Box 40)
- Distribution Sheets, Aug 1967 - June 1969 (Box 40)
- Religion Department, Feb 1941 - Sep 1962 (Box 40)
- NYS Education Dept.: English Summer Institute, 1964-1965 (Box 40)
- NYS Education Dept.: English Summer Institute (proposed - not given), 1964-1965 (Box 40)
- NYS Education Dept.: Language Arts (Reading) Institute (English,), 1964-1965 (Box 40)
- NYS Education Dept.: Latin, Workshop for Teachers, Mar 1964 (Box 40)
- NYS Education Dept.: Latin-American Studies, 1963-1964 (Box 40)
- NYS Education Dept.: Math Program, Evening, 1962 (Box 40)
- NYS Education Dept.: Russian Program, Evening, 1960-1964; (3 folders) (Box 40)
- NYS Education Dept.: Russian Program, Summer (not given in 1962), 1961, 1965-1966 (Box 40)
- NYS Education Dept.: Science Institute, Proposed, Spring 1965 (Box 40)
- Art Dept., 1960-1965 (Box 40)
- Biology Dept., 1958-1965 (Box 40)
- Chemistry Dept., 1961-1965 (Box 40)
- Classics Dept., 1962-1965 (Box 40)
- Drama Dept., 1954-1965 (Box 40)
- English Dept., 1961-1965 (Box 40)
- French Dept., 1961-1965 (Box 40)
- Geology, 1963-1965 (Box 40)
- German Dept., 1961-1965 (Box 40)
- History Dept., 1961-1965 (Box 40)
- Italian Dept., 1961-1965 (Box 40)
- Math, 1961-1965 (Box 40)
- Music Dept., 1961-1965 (Box 40)
- Philosophy Dept., 1956-1965 (Box 40)
- Physical Education Dept., 1960-1965 (Box 40)
- Political Science, 1961-1965 (Box 40)
- Physics Dept., 1949-1965 (Box 40)
- Psychology Dept., 1960-1965 (Box 40)
- Religion Dept., 1961-1965 (Box 40)
- Spanish Dept., 1961-1965 (Box 40)
- Russian Dept., 1963-1965 (Box 40)
- "The Role of Higher Education in the Development of the Hudson Valley Region" (Box 40)
- Minimum Conditions for Satisfactory Teaching (Box 40)
- Poughkeepsie Action Committee (Box 40)
- Vassar College Governance (Box 40)
- Proposed Governance (Box 40)
- Governance - Miscellaneous (Box 40)
- Certification for MAT Program (Box 40)
- MSA - MAT and TED (Box 41)
- NYS Requirements - Elementary (Box 41)
- BC Charter (Box 41)
- Albany White Paper on Urban Education, 1967 (Box 41)
- "Imperatives for Change" (annotated) (Box 41)
- Federal, (9 folders) (Box 41)
- Vassar College, (19 folders) (Box 41)
- MAT Others (Box 41)
- Financial Physical (Box 41)
- Elementary MAT (Box 41)
- Departments, (5 folders) (Box 41)
- SUNY, (5 folders) (Box 41)
- Venezuelan Visa Documents (Box 41)
- Venezuelan Women at Vassar (Box 41)
- Faculty Load, (3 folders) (Box 41)
- Meetings - Miscellaneous (Box 41)
- Computer (Automaton), 1965-1969; (2 folders) (Box 41)
- Chapman's Report on Sex Differences (Box 41)
- CCEP Minutes, 1957-1959; (3 folders) (Box 42)
- CCEP, Topical (Box 42)
- Area Studies, 1951-1965 (Box 42)
- Admissions, 1958-1968 (Box 42)
- Alumnae Association, 1963-1969 (Box 42)
- Off-Campus Studies, May 1968 - Dec 1968 (Box 42)
- Special Students, 1968-1969 (Box 42)
- Workload, (3 folders) (Box 42)
- Chemistry Summer Institute (Box 42)
- Public Affairs - Committee on Faculty-Student Research (Box 42)
- Blodgett Library (Box 42)
- New College (Box 42)
- Files [sent] to Storage [in] 1988: CCEP Coordinating Committee on Educational Policy, 1957-1959 (Box 42)
- CCEP Report and extra copies, 1959; (2 folders) (Box 42)
- CCEP Minutes, 1957 (Box 43)
- Cashin Report, "Higher Educational Needs in the Mid-Hudson Region,", 1969 (Box 43)
- Middle States Report of the Evaluation of Vassar College, 1958 (Box 43)
- Files [sent] to Storage [in] 1988: Financial Planning Committee, 1970-1972; (2 folders) (Box 43)
- Faculty Salary Recommendations [personnel], 1969-1970 (Box 43)
- Faculty Salary Budget [personnel], 1971-1972 (Box 43)
- Department Recommendations [personnel], 1970-1971; (4 folders) (Box 43)
- Academic Budget, 1970-1972; (3 folders) (Box 43)
- Faculty Reviews [personnel], 1977-1978; (3 folders) (Box 43)
- MSA, (5 folders) (Box 43)
- Appendices to the Report of the Comprehensive Planning Committee, 1968 (Box 43)
- Middle States Evaluation Part B: 11-30, E.A. Clark, (2 folders) (Box 43)
- Files [sent] to Storage [in] 1988: Departmental December Recommendations, 1970-1971; (4 folders) (Box 44)
- Faculty Salary Evaluations [personnel], 1977-1979; (3 folders) (Box 44)
- Salary Recommendations [personnel], 1978 (Box 44)
- Committee Files Academic Panel Through Library (Box 44)
- Committee Lists and Functions (Box 44)
- Ad Hoc Committee on Review Procedures (Box 44)
- Administrative Budget Committee (Box 44)
- Committee on Admission (Box 44)
- Advisory Committee, 1947-1971 (Box 44)
- Advisory Committee - Faculty Salary Budget (Box 44)
- Advisory Committee - General (Box 44)
- Advisory Committee - Governance Revision (Box 44)
- Advisory Committee - Promotions, Tenure (Box 44)
- Advisory Committee on Computer Literacy Grant Program (FIPSE) (Box 44)
- Committee on the Afro-American Cultural Center (ad hoc) (Box 44)
- Committee, American Culture on Investment Responsibility (Box 44)
- Committee, Faculty Common on Black Studies (Box 44)
- Advisory Committee on Black Administrative Appointments (Box 44)
- Committee on Buildings and Grounds (Box 44)
- Committee on Coeducation for the Future (Box 44)
- College Council Committee (Box 44)
- Committees on Committees (Box 44)
- Ad Hoc Lecture Committee (Box 44)
- American Culture on Poynter Fellows Committee (Box 44)
- Student Committee on Black Studies (Box 44)
- College Regulations Committee (Box 45)
- Dean-Student Conference Committee (Box 45)
- Committee on Energy Conservation (ad hoc) (Box 45)
- Ethnics Committee (Box 45)
- Faculty Compensation Committee, (2 folders) (Box 45)
- Committee on Faculty Procedures, (2 folders) (Box 45)
- Computer Acquisition Committee (Box 45)
- Computers Users' Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 45)
- Files [sent] to Storage [in] 1988, Board of Trustees Minutes, 1960-1963; (3 folders) (Box 45)
- Executive Committee Minutes, 1960-1967; (5 folders) (Box 45)
- Retirement Policy, AADEA Law and Interpretation Bulletins, 1980 (Box 45)
- Retirement Policy, Age Profile and Retirement Parallels, 1980 (Box 45)
- Retirement Policy, AAUP/AAC Start of Plan, 1980 (Box 45)
- Retirement Policy, Social Security Benefits, 1980 (Box 45)
- Retirement Policy, Standard Early Retirement Plan, 1980 (Box 45)
- Financial Picture of Vassar, 1973; (2 folders) (Box 45)
- CPC Report, 1968 (Box 45)
- Retirement Policy: TIAA Retirement Study, 1980 (Box 45)
- Retirement, miscellaneous (Box 45)
- Board of Trustees Minutes, 1963-1967; (3 folders) (Box 46)
- Departmental Reports, Requests and Proposals, (4 folders) (Box 46)
- Academic Panel and Court, 1944-1953 (Box 46)
- Administrative Group Minutes, 1958-1961 (Box 46)
- Committee on Admission, 1941-1960; (4 folders) (Box 46)
- Admissions Study, 1951 (Box 46)
- Admissions Pamphlets (Box 46)
- Alumnae, 1952-1955 (Box 46)
- American College Council, Summer Study Abroad, 1953-1958 (Box 46)
- American Culture Program (Box 46)
- "A" miscellaneous (Box 46)
- Vassar Business Week Article, 1956 (Box 46)
- China Institute (Box 46)
- Cold Spring Project, 1952-1953 (Box 46)
- College Government Association and Senate, 1956-1958 (Box 46)
- College Religious Association, 1953-1957 (Box 46)
- Commencement, 1943-1947 (Box 46)
- Commencement Programs, 1929-1948 (Box 46)
- Coordinating Committee (Box 46)
- Departmental Reports, Requests and Proposals, (18 folders) (Box 47)
- Extra copies of mimeographed materials from the Student Curriculum Committee, (3 folders) (Box 47)
- Statistical Summary of Time Record of Vassar Colleges Students, 1939-1943 (Box 47)
- Alumnae Certificates and Testimonials, n.d. - 1941 (Box 47)
- Comptroller File, 1942-1948 (Box 47)
- File from the Endowment Committee (Box 47)
- College Government and Senate Association, 1946-1950 (Box 47)
- Files [sent] to Storage [in] 1988: Board of Trustees Meetings, 1984 (Box 47)
- Michael Graves Building Program - Art Gallery, (2 folders) (Box 47)
- Cambridge Associates Report to Trustees (Box 47)
- Vassar Quarterly LXXII No. 3, 1947 (Box 47)
- Faculty Tenure, miscellaneous (Box 47)
- Cambridge Associates Financial Equilibrium Project Draft, 1981 (Box 48)
- Cambridge Associates Final Draft, 1982 (Box 48)
- Committee on Curricular Polices, 1966-1975; (15 folders) (Box 48)
- Files [sent] to Storage [in] 1988: Annual Report, 1965-1968; (3 folders) (Box 48)
- Cambridge Associates Inc., A Study of Financial Equilibrium Draft, 28 Jan 1982 (Box 48)
- MSA: Report of the Evaluation of VC, Mar 1958 (Box 48)
- Annual Report, 1978-1982; (8 folders) (Box 49)
- Various Department and Programs Annual Reports (Box 49)
- Miscellaneous Budgets, 1960-1963 (Box 49)
- Subcommittees’ Reports to CCP (Box 49)
- Miscellaneous Reports, 1980-1984 (Box 49)
- Admissions (Box 49)
- Action Council (Box 49)
- Admissions Questionnaire (Box 49)
- Alumnae (Box 49)
- Alumnae Magazine Article (Box 49)
- Allied Medical Services (Box 49)
- CCP Minutes, 1975-1980; (9 folders) (Box 50)
- Alumnae Council Speech (Draft – Not Used) (Box 50)
- Alumnae Council Speech (Box 50)
- American Council on Education (Box 50)
- Alumnae Questionnaire (Mrs. Kohl’s Materials) (Box 50)
- Alumnae Questionnaire Material (Box 50)
- Arts (Box 50)
- Art Conservation Graduate Program (Box 50)
- Subcommittee on Alternatives (Box 50)
- Bowdoin College Notes (Box 50)
- Brooklyn Polytechnic Institute (Box 50)
- Building Plans (Box 50)
- Business (Box 50)
- Calendar (Box 50)
- Catalyst (Box 50)
- Center for Advanced Studies (Box 50)
- CEEB (Box 50)
- The Cluster College Concept, 1967 (Box 50)
- College Research Center (Box 50)
- Committee on New Dimensions (CND) (Box 50)
- CND (Box 50)
- CCP Minutes, 1980; (3 folders) (Box 51)
- Public Affairs – GSPIA (Box 51)
- Public Affairs – Vassar Institute (Box 51)
- Requests for Material (Box 51)
- Residential Plan (Box 51)
- Responses from Departments (Box 51)
- Speech by R.A. Rosenbaum (Box 51)
- Field Work, Miscellaneous (Box 51)
- Schedule (Box 51)
- Science Center and Programs (Box 51)
- Senior Center Council Report to Faculty (Box 51)
- Speech – EAD, 1967 (Box 51)
- Social Work Program (Box 51)
- State of New York (Box 51)
- SUNY, (2 folders) (Box 51)
- SUNY New Paltz (Box 51)
- SUNY Printed Material (Box 51)
- Steering Committee (Box 51)
- Student Committees (Box 51)
- Summer Program (Box 51)
- Past Travel, Conferences, etc. (Box 51)
- Future Travel, Conferences, etc. (Box 51)
- “Undergrad. Ed.” – Report to Faculty (Box 51)
- Undergraduate Program (Box 51)
- VC and Poughkeepsie (Box 51)
- The VC Student (Box 51)
- Vassar-Yale Study, (4 folders) (Box 51)
- VC Miscellany News (Box 51)
- Vacational Bureau (Box 51)
- Warthin Proposal (Box 51)
- Wescott and Ranzani Project (Box 51)
- Yale Admissions (Box 51)
- "The Younger Generation" – An RIA Survey of College Students (Box 51)
- New Dimensions Minutes (Box 51)
- Various files [sent to storage in 1967] including: Planning figures- Dutchess County (Box 52)
- Pre-professional Programs (Box 52)
- Publicity (Box 52)
- Public Affairs (comparative) (Box 52)
- Faculty-Elected Committee Minutes, (2 folders) (Box 52)
- Foreign Study, Field Work, Work Study (Box 52)
- CND (Box 52)
- CND: Report on Alternatives, 1967 (Box 52)
- CND: Xeroxed Material (Box 52)
- Computer Training (Box 52)
- Computer Assisted Instruction (Box 52)
- Continuing Education (Box 52)
- Coordinate College (Box 52)
- CND – Mrs. Daniels’ Report (Box 52)
- CND – Working Papers (Box 52)
- Communications – Board of Trustees (Box 52)
- Conference – Women and the World of Tomorrow (Box 52)
- Correspondence (Box 52)
- Costs (Box 52)
- Curriculum Committee (Box 52)
- Diagrams (Box 52)
- EAD – Personal (Box 52)
- EAD – Speech Material, (2 folders) (Box 52)
- EAD and EAC Trip to Washington (Box 52)
- Educational Philosophy (Box 52)